<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.11</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 3.1.1.51 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://pad.asp-software.org</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>miorsoft</Company_Name>
		<Address_1 />
		<Address_2 />
		<City_Town />
		<State_Province />
		<Zip_Postal_Code />
		<Country>Italy</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>https://miorsoft.github.io/Site/index.html</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Roberto</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Mior</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>reexre@gmail.com</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Roberto</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Mior</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>reexre@gmail.com</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>reexre@gmail.com</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>reexre@gmail.com</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>reexre@gmail.com</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone />
			<Support_Phone />
			<General_Phone />
			<Fax_Phone />
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>PhotoModularFX</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>0.3.226</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>11</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>14</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2016</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Demo</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Win8,Win10,Win7 x32,Win7 x64,WinOther,WinServer,WinVista,WinVista x64,WinXP,Other</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info>[Nodes]
-New Split: Split Channel in 2 halfs (useful for stereo images)
-New Split3: Split 3channels image in 2 halfs (useful for stereo images)
-New POW3: Power of 3 Channels (Like Pow)
-New SpinBLUR: Spin Blur
-New SpinBLUR3: Spin Blur 3 channels
-New RGB>Yxy: RGB to Yxy colorspace conversion
-New Yxy>RGB: Yxy to RGB colorspace conversion
-New HeatMap: Grayscale to HeatMap(rgb)
-New Sorting: Pixel Sorting effect.
-New Solarize: Classic Solarization Filter
-New Solarize3: Classic Solarization Filter
-New OilPaint: Classic OilPainting
-New OilPaint3: Classic OilPainting (RGB)
-New Chroma: Chromaticty colorspace conversion
-New LocalTHR: Local Threshold Binarization
-New LocalOTSU: Experimental Local Otsu
-New Noise2: 3 Levels noise
-DoG: Picture borders fix (Call 2 Blurs instead of in-built blurs)
-HSL: Colorspace conversion added: Darel Rex Finley "HSP"
-StdDEV, TODO StdDEV3: Revisited
[Other] 
-Small bug fix of "Keep same Zoom factor at Program Restart" in some systems.
-Allow more than 3 outputs for Nodes (max 6)
-Fix missing "Background" Folder in Package(s)
-New PopUp-Message Widget.
-Small Interface restyles
</Program_Change_Info>
		<Program_Specific_Category>Graphics</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>Graphic Apps::Editors</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_System_Requirements />
		<File_Info>
			<File_Size_Bytes>69263349</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>67639</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>66.05</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count />
			<Expire_Based_On />
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>Photo effect, modular, custom, fx,image, pitcure, advanced, modularity, flow,Photo Effect Filter, Chain, Manipulation</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Portable Photo effects creator</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Portable Photo effects creator</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Portable Photo effects creator</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Generate impressive, custom photo effects by manually configuring the steps of the image manipulation process, in this reliable program. PhotoModularFX allows you to quickly and easily create photo effects, using parallel processing flow that you can customize at any time. The modular nature of the program allows you to add multiple photo editing processes and to tweak them to obtain the desired effect.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>PhotoModularFX allows you to quickly and easily create photo effects, using parallel processing flow that you can customize at any time. The modular nature of the program allows you to add multiple photo editing processes and to tweak them to obtain the desired effect.

PhotoModularFX features a dynamic parallel photo processor that supports several manipulation modules. Moreover, you can preview the picture, in the main window, at any time, by simply sliding the cursor to the upper left corner.

The program features a large list of preset modules that you can add to the processing strings. They are basic effects, such as Blur, Border, Dithering, FakeHDR, Invert, K-mean or Paint, to name a few, that you can easily customize.

Moreover, you can select one of the available templates or create your own processing string, starting with the Input module.

PhotoModularFX includes numerous modules, including color space conversion tools, noise reduction filters or image distortion algorithms.

You may also use some of the special modules, for example FLOW Difference of Gaussians (DoG F), local tone mapping or K-mean CLUSTER, which support heavy customization. You can blur edges, adjust colors and highlight contours in order to obtain stylized images.

Other advanced filters include POW, which allows you to control the image luminance, PYRAMID, a level-detail adjustment tool, Smooth or color Temperature. The program includes a detailed documentation that explains the effects configuration modes.

PhotoModularFX allows you to insert several filters in the editing process, then interconnect them using the MIX tools or nature filters. One of the remarkable features of PhotoModularFX is that it writes the effects and parameters in the output file. In other words, when you export the photo, you do not only save the result, but the process as well. You may load the picture when you wish to use the same algorithm again.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>https://miorsoft.github.io/Site/PhotoModularFX/index.html</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL />
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/51621154/Screenshot/Screenshot 2016-11-13 19.07.32.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/51621154/MIORSOFT/PMfx/ICON_4.ico</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/51621154/photomodularfx.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/51621154/PhotoModularFX.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/51621154/PhotoModularFX - LITE.zip</Secondary_Download_URL>
			<Additional_Download_URL_1>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/51621154/PhotoModularFX Portable SelfExtractor.exe</Additional_Download_URL_1>
			<Additional_Download_URL_2>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/51621154/PhotoModularFX LITE Portable SelfExtractor.exe</Additional_Download_URL_2>
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>The Demo version of PhotoModularFX can be freely distributed over the internet in an unchanged form</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS 'AS IS' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL MiorSoft/'Roberto Mior' BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</EULA>
	</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
